propakistani.pk 2016-06-09

# Privacy Policy - ProPakistani

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for all pages and services offered by ProPakistani.PK

 **» Personally Provided Information  
**

You do not have to give us personal information to visit ProPakistani.PK. If you choose to provide us with additional information through an e-mail message, inquiry form, comments, etc., we will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question, inquiry, or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not give, share, sell or transfer any personal information to a third party.

 **» Website Traffic Analysis Software  
**

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We also monitor our traffic to analyze visitors’s information, such as, but not limited to, operating system, browsers, screen resolutions and similar.

In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

 **» E-mail Newsletters**

If users wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for contact information. Our Daily Newsletter is powered by FeedBurner, however we use in-house solution for weekly Newsletter. We/Feedburner use information submitted by you in the same manner as we use contact information described above. Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the e-mail newsletter.

 **SMS Subscription**

You are asked to provider certain information if you request to receive daily SMS alerts. We collect this information to keep our SMS broadcast as per the dynamics of our subscribers. Like all other instances, this information will never be given/sold to third party, otherwise asked by the the Law of the Land.

 **Third Party Advertising Partners**

All users of ProPakistani.PK must keep this in mind that third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving on ProPakistani.PK.

For, instance one of our partners, Google uses the [ DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.google.com/doubleclick/) on ProPakistani.PK displaying AdSense for content ads. Similarly, other advertising partners may use their respective cookies to track advertising stats.

 **» External Links**

Our web sites contain links to other sites. ProPakistani.PK is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personal information.

 **Disclaimer**

 **USE OF WEB SITE MATERIALS.**

All contents, web site design, text, logos, sound, images, graphics, and the selection and arrangement thereof, and all other elements of the ProPakistani.PK Web Site are the sole and exclusive property of ProPakistani.PK, and are protected by copyright, intellectual property, trade dress and other applicable laws and may not be copied, modified, published, imitated, distributed, or transmitted in whole or in part without the prior written consent of ProPakistani.PK.

Please report any such instances of use to legal@propakistani.pk

 **Disclaimer Press Release:**

ProPakistani.pk receive many press releases from PR Agencies and Companies or other related parties. We do do not accept any responsibility for the accuracy and completeness for any information provided in the press releases. Being a leading Telecom & Technology blog we publish them.

We Reserve the right to make necessary changes in PR (if required) and we reserve the right to reject or remove old PR anytime without any notice.

 **Note:** This Page can get updated any time, without an prior noitce, so keep checking back.

Last updated: September 19th, 2012
